Kouban
Prefectural
High
School
Episode 3               Lessons in Love?
Oh, Senpai.
What are you reading there?
The Perfect Guide to Dating
Start with
the basics!
After today, I'll be a hit
with the chicks...
My dream of a harem will soon be a reality!
Nanakura, I understand how
girls think now thanks to this book!
Then do you understand why I'm angry?
I wish you knew why I was mad!
You too, Spoiled-chan?!
Hang on, wait, just a sec...
Because I said something stupid again?
That's half right.
Honestly, I just wish I was in love.
Does that mean you're not right now?
Not that I've noticed.
I don't know how to feel about that...
I mean, it all started
with the bits that we do.
They might just be bits,
but you're serious about the acting, right?
Which gets me thinking
about who I would choose during class...
Wow, you're really happy!
Oh, but I think I might understand why.
It's because I praised your acting!
Bzzt!
Okay, your makeup's done, Nanakura-san.
Or maybe "Class President Nanakura"?
Thank you for everything.
I can face my duties now,
with your help.
She can really switch it on
in an instant. Such an actress.
Hey, you've got a different vibe.
It's really helping me get
into the role of class president.
Nice.
A relationship with a serious class
president type would be awesome.
First thing I'd do is join the
student council to get closer to her...
Do you honestly think you can function
in student government with ulterior motives?
Sorry!
He backed down so easily!
Kind of hard for the conversation
to go anywhere if you do that...
I feel like I'm the kinda guy who'd get
purged from the student council, anyway.
On second thought,
your application will be accepted.
My goal is to create a school
where everyone
can look forward to
attending class, after all.
Class President... your hand is so soft!
You can't just say
things like that, Senpai!
What would you do if you really
were class president?
Let me think...
I'd like there to be classes
that mixed grades could attend.
You mean like first-years and
third-years in the same classroom?
Correct.
It'd increase exchange between
students outside of extracurriculars.
Man, that's a legit president-type proposal.
So, what are you really after?
Theoretically... just,
speaking theoretically!
Someone could then share a class
with an upperclassman they have a crush on...
I'm pretty sure illicit romantic relationships
are a bad idea for a class president!
Oh, that's the club president.
It's a good likeness!
Ain't it though?
He's good at doing caricatures.
Want me to draw you, Nanakura?
Done!
Thank you so much!
What a glare!
That's Cool-chan!
Do I really look so aggressive?
Well, the trick is taking characteristic
traits and emphasizing them.
This is kind of embarrassing...
I drew Imp-chan too!
That's a literal devil!
Staaare
I'm not even sure looking at me
is serving a purpose, considering...
Oh, cute!
This one is cute!
Yeah? You are pretty cute, Nanakura!
The drawing! I was talking
about your drawing!
C'mon, no need to be modest.
That's not...
It really really really really
isn't what I meant!
Kouban
Prefectural
High
School
Nanakura, do you act differently in the club
compared to when you're with your classmates?
I don't think so.
But maybe I seem a bit different
because I'm not trying to be polite.
So, try being casual with me, then!
FOREIGN RESIDENCE
Let's start by talking about movies.
You seen "Foreign Residence?"
I have not...
You have not?
I mean, nah.
That's a horror movie,
y'know? Way too scary.
It seriously is scary, too.
I'm impressed you can stand them...
Eh, it's an educational thing.
They tend to do a lot of stuff with sets...
Maybe you could study
the acting bits, Nanakura.
No! No way! I just can't!
Well, what if we watched one together?
Do you mind if I cry the entire time...?
That might not be great.
This feels like we're dating! I love it!
Having a more casual conversation
with you is pretty refreshing.
Although it does feel like I've taken
a hit to my senpai aura, though.
I totally respect you, though, Senpai.
Huh? You're still being casual?
I think I'll keep this up for this week.
Oh, you're enjoying yourself, aren't you?
No... it's Senpai!
Is he alone? I wanna talk to him...
I wish I was better dressed.
Hey, it's Nanakura!
W-W-Wha... Wha... you...
Kouban High School
Drama Club
Senpai... that shirt...
We made those for the culture festival.
Come on, Nanakura, you're
not exactly dressed up either!
I don't really follow fashion trends.
Is it weird?
N-No, it's not...
But if you need advice,
you wanna go shopping together?
I do.
Then again, given how we're both dressed,
we probably won't end up
picking anything decent!
I normally dress perfectly fine!
You saying I'm the only unfashionable one?
W... Would you please go
clothes shopping with me?
Hey, Nanakura, are you
growing your hair out?
No...
I'm thinking about getting a cut,
but I haven't been able to make up my mind
about how short I want it.
A new 'do, huh. I can see
why you'd wanna be careful.
You had better say it's cute.
I... I couldn't say something
that embarrassing...
Then again, if you had short hair...
Let me imagine it for a sec.
But at what cost?! The pigtails!
He seems more anxious about it than me now.
I don't like how much maintenance it takes
to keep it under control when it's long.
You put the work
in when no one's looking, huh?
That's admirable!
I can tell your ends and texture
are on another level.
Do head rubs usually make you clam up?
I don't think I'll cut
it short, after all...
So, you want to be actors, huh?
I like your ambition.
We've got new members.
Since they wanna be acting,
that makes them your kouhai, Nanakura.
Make sure to help them out if they need it.
I wonder if I'll be able to...
If you can't give good advice, they'll
stop asking you about stuff in general.
I don't like the sound of that.
Huh, have I ever asked you for advice...?
How can I become the kind of
senpai people rely on?
In your case, I'd suggest...
Maybe taking things a bit more seriously.
But that's not meant to be
a rejection of how you normally act.
Is that... Demure-chan?
Was it mature enough?
It sure as heck was!
Yay!
You've got a total babyface now, though.
Gonna have to work on that.
H-Hang on a second...
Hey, Nanakura, I could
use some more advice...
I can't do it if you make me laugh!
It's not quite steady.
I see.
Are you going to remake it?
I bet Tsundere-chan isn't great
with heights, huh?
That's your concern?!
This isn't even that high up!
Quit shaking it! That's actually dangerous!
Come on. I need
to reinforce it, so get down.
Y-You want me to... jump down?
That's fine too. I'll hold you steady.
That's...
I'd have to be like "Fwump"
and I'll be "Eek" and then "Ahhh!"
I don't know if I can pull that off cutely!
What are you talking about?!
Hang on. Wait, wait, wait....
This is really, really, really scary!
Senpai, don't shake it!
Just wait a sec!
I'm not doing anything! What is with you?!
What are you two up to?
Prez! Help!
Pseudo Harem
Pseudo
Harem
Class 4-1
It's you, Senpai!
That was when I was in fourth grade.
Was that a shutter?
Seriously, what?
There you are!
You seem to be having a ton of fun
with those rolls in your hands.
I was really hyped about
that breakfast buffet.
Another one?!
Who gets that happy
over something like that?
I'd ask who doesn't get hype for a buffet!
Seeing you so happy puts me
in a good mood, too.
I mean, I wouldn't act like
that at this age!
Buffets are really fun, though...
I'm sure I would've
liked him back then, too.
Shouldn't you be in the
gymnasium, Miss Star Actress?
Maybe I'll skip.
I can see how Imp-chan would skip out on—
Hang on.
Are you hijacking Nanakura's normal life?
I was rehearsing all day
yesterday, so she just kinda...
Is this like, you're having
trouble getting out of character?
That must be rough.
So, can I stick around and bug you?
Nanakura... has she developed
a will of her own?
Imp-chan is gonna take
advantage of me at this rate!
She will not!
You sure?
But if I tried, would you let me?
What are you doing, Senpai?!
That was Imp-chan's fault!
Not being able to shake off a character...
maybe you're practicing too hard!
I'm so sorry for getting in the way.
Do you have an idea for how to fix this?
I think portraying another
character might work...
I should probably head
to practice after all.
Nanakura?
Rehearsal's started.
She's not here.
Maybe she's taking the day off?
Probably.
Let's go, then.
I guess we should.
Maybe Imp-chan was right.
You could use a break, Nanakura.
Let's skip club together.
Especially since my thumb hurts
too much to get any work done.
Let's get you to the nurse's office, now!
That's your old coat, right, Senpai?
Sure is.
It was used as a costume
and then they returned it to me.
Did you do that thing
at middle school graduation,
where you give the second button
to someone you like, or vice versa?
What is that? I've never heard of it before.
Wait, does this mean everyone else did it?!
Seems likely...
Is that different from confessing normally?
I'm not sure.
We're graduating today,
so I want you to have this, Nanakura.
Well? What do you think?
I didn't really catch it all.
Could you do it again?
But that was a really good take!
Just one more time!
Will you accept my second button...
Imp-chan?
She's not in today!
But it's graduation!
No love letters today...
Good!
That means no hearts for me to break.
Senpai, haven't you been
doing that act every morning?
Any time is a good time
to polish your acting skills.
But Senpai... you're in the props department.
Actually getting one was so much
of a shock I was speechless!
Is this for real?
It's like a dream.
Imp-chan
Tsundere-chan
It was a dream!
I was kind of hoping your shoe box
would stay empty forever!
I was kind of hoping your shoe
box would stay empty forever!
She's saying she doesn't want me to
accept anyone else's love letters, right?!
Do you really need me
to spell it out for you?
You just looked really desperate for a love letter!
That's all! That's the only reason!
So don't get any weird ideas!
You just looked really
desperate for a love letter!
That's all! That's the only reason!
So don't get any weird ideas!
Weird ideas?
But I had weird ideas before
I even opened the envelope...
You had better write a response, too.
I got it covered!
This town's about to have
a letter paper shortage!
Then again, we are in a paperless age...
What are you talking about?
Someone who got love letters from
these two would have a hard call to make!
It's a good thing they
were just pretend, then.
I'm gonna cherish them anyway!
Especially since it's unlikely
I'll ever get any more!
Oh shoot, my treasures...
"Dear Kitahama-senpai.
It's a little embarrassing to go out of my
way to write this down as a letter.
The time I spend
with you is always such fun,
and even outside of club—"
But I hadn't finished reading it yet!
I... didn't mean to actually send this one!
Let me finish reading it!
I-I-It's too embarrassing, so no!
Please forget you ever saw it!
I understand.
But I think I'll need to read it
once to properly forget it!
I said no!
Senpai!
Good afternoon!
You seem to be in a good mood.
I helped a friend resolve
some romantic trouble.
Relationship advice, huh?
Well, considering you've got five romance
experts bouncing around in your head.
Don't make them sound like
alternate personalities...
I don't think anyone would ever turn
to me for that kinda advice.
If you had feelings for someone that you
don't have a lot of shared interests with,
how would you approach them?
I'd try hard.
Are you sure you're just not
that interested in dating, Senpai?
Hard to say.
But if that's how the romance
master sees it, maybe it's true.
I can see the appeal, y'know?!
I wanna have my heart pound
and butterflies in my stomach, too!
I don't really think you'd act that way,
even if you did fall in love
with someone, Senpai.
If the master thinks so,
then it's probably true.
He's accepting everything I say!
Also, in this master's opinion,
I think you'd be better off
with someone younger...
Definitely.
If you say so, Master, then I bet it's true.
Wait, are you saying...
That I should get into little girls?!
I didn't mean that much younger!
Much Ado About Nothing
Much
Ado
About Nothing!
Hello, Kitaha...
I mean, Nanakura residence.
I think it might be better
the other way around!
He's sticking to this premise
of him marrying into my family.